AKSHAY NETAKE

I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. With 3+ yrs of experience as a professional Web developer, I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I can handle project from scratch to production with smart sprint planning and executing it. Having a strong knowledge about frontend as well as backend.

At/Post: Wakavali, Tal: Dapoli Ratnagiri, Maharastra 9403641147 akshay.netake@gmail.com akshaynetake.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Indiawyn Gaming pvt. ltd., Mumbai — backend Intern

NOV 2018 - JAN 2019

Worked as a Backend Developer to develop Backend for games in python flask Framework.

Inspeero Technologies, Mumbai — Software Developer

JUL 2019 - AUG 2021

Build digital tools that empower businesses, apps that leverage new-age technologies and design strategies

Moshi Moshi Media, Bangalore — Software Developer

AUG 2021 - PRESENT

Advertising agency that works closely with Startups and MNC's.

EDUCATION

Saraswati College of Engineering, KHARGHAR — BE

JUN 2015 - MAY 2019

Score 7.15

Rotary English Medium School , KHED - TWELE

MAR 2015

Score 73.9

JNV Ratnagiri, RAJAPUR — TENTH

MAR 2013

Score 79.6

SKILLS

- REACT JS
- NODE JS
- ANGULAR
- REACT NATIVE
- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- CSS
- MONGODB
- MYSQL
- PHP
- FIREBASE
- PYTHON

KEY SKILLS

- Software Development
- Requirement Gathering
- Unit Testing
- Agile Methodology
- Code Optimization
- REST APIs
- Documentation
- Coordination
- Troubleshooting
- Automation

LANGUAGES

- MARATHI
- ENGLISH
- HINDI

PROJECTS

WNS — HTML, CSS, PHP

First Project as a Production Website development for WNS which is global service based company

UNSYNED — Angular, Nodejs, MongoDB

Artist portal where artists can upload there music files and admin will accept the music files and by votes automatically user will get chosen

Glance — Angular, Nodejs, MongoDB

Dating App which is launched in USA and Canada help to find the match while just sending blinks and limited time for chat.

The Cover Foundry — React JS, Nodejs, MongoDB

Artist portal where artists can upload their songs and normal users can listen while customizing the song like only drum, drum with guitar etc.

Tastee — React Js, Nodejs, MongoDB

The app for Foodtrucks and restaurants so normal users can see the locations of vendors and also see promotions and menus.

Kusa Education — Angular, Nodejs, MongoDB

Online platform where students can find teachers of any country at any time and interact with them.

Ohieo — Next JS

Online Platform to order food from ohio catering services for different events and functions.

We Chimni — Angular, Nodejs, MongoDB

Online Platform to sell HandCrafted Products and also homemade things for the women empowerment.

Toit — Angular

Personal website for Great handcrafted beers and an unforgettable brewpub experience.

Digital Harbor — React JS

Fancy website to show product services.